An inquisitive and diligent computer scientist student specializing in Application Development at Renton Technical College. Intuitive, passionate, and high potential, with interests working in Front-end, Back-end, Full-Stack Development, UX Design, and all things Software. Jonathan Mantello is an ideal member for a team of motivated problem solvers.

Phone: (206) 280 – 9135

Email: jonathan.mantello@gmail.com
School Email: jcmantello@student.rtc.edu

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jonathan-mantello/

Web Portfolio: https://jmantellowebportfolio.netlify.app/

Experience:

Guided Pathways IDEAL Fellowship Scholar, Rooted In Love Education - Summer 2021

Engaged with student leaders across Washington State community colleges in the development of racial and social
justice advocacy skills through comprehensive research and proposing innovative solutions to complex problems of
inequity within college policies.

Tutor, LRCC at Renton Technical College, April 2021 - October 2021

• Tutored computer science students with assignments and reinforced computer science concepts.

ASG Senate, Renton Technical College, February 2021 – Present

• Represent student interests to college administration, Organize student committees to enhance the student experience, and allocate district resources appropriately.

Audio and Visual Technician, Avidex Event Technologies, November 2018 - May 2020

- Understudy as Warehouse Manager, Responsible for managing the installation and shipping and receiving departments and receiving all inventory for both Seattle and Bellevue locations.
- Communicate project requirements and scope with project managers and team leads.
- Maintain a detailed log of the items received and the associated installation projects.
- Learned through informal training as well as learn on the job.
- Set up, maintain, and dismantle audio and video for live and recorded events, working independently and in teams.

Education:

Bachelor of Applied Science in Application Development, Renton Technical College, Anticipated June 2024

- Cumulative GPA: 3.99
- · Vice-President's Honors List

Associate of Applied Arts and Sciences in Digital Audio Engineering, Shoreline Community College, September 2015 - June 2018

Cumulative GPA: 3.60Graduated with Honors

Job-Related Skills:

Programming Languages: Java, SQL, C#, HTML, CSS.

Tools: NetBeans, Visual Studio, SQL Server Management, GitHub, Word, Excel, Microsoft Teams.

Soft Skills: Friendly, Communicative, Organized, Motivated, Positive, Engaged, Collaborative, Inquisitive.

Hard Skills: Problem Solving, Computer Programming, Object-Oriented Design, Front-End Web Development, Computer Troubleshooting, Database Design and Management, Clean Coding, Skill Acquisition.